eatnow.com.au 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy | eatnow.com.au

#### 1\. Privacy Statement

**1.1** Eat Now Services Pty Ltd (Eat Now) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. Our privacy policy outlines our approach to privacy and how we collect, use and protect your personal information. It also sets out your rights in relation to accessing the personal information we collect and hold about you. We are bound by the Australian Privacy Principles (or APPs) in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). 

**1.2** Personal information is defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and means information or an opinion about an identified individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable. 

**1.3** Our Website may contain links to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of each website you visit. 

#### 2\. Collection of Personal Information

**2.1** Eat Now only collects personal information for the purposes of conducting our business as an online service provider. The personal information we collect from you will include information you give us when you:

(a) register or subscribe to our Website;

(b) complete a transaction with us; or

(c) contact us.

**2.2** The personal information that we collect on individuals may include, but is not limited to: 

(a) your name;

(b) your contact details including your email, home address and billing address;

(c) your payment details; and

(d) other personal information that we collect in the course of a transaction or that you provide to us when you contact us.

**2.3** We may collect personal information from individuals who are not customers of our business but whose personal information is given to us by those individuals via our Website or in the course of a transaction

**2.4** Where reasonably practicable, we attempt to collect information directly from individuals. When we collect information, we will generally explain to the individual why we are collecting it, who we give it to and how we will use or disclose it or, alternatively, those matters will be obvious from the circumstances.

**2.5** If we collect information about an individual from someone else, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that the individual is made aware of the matters listed in clause 2.4.

**2.6** We will collect personal information from you by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably intrusive way.

#### Use of Cookies and third party advertising and analytics

**2.7** When you visit our Website, we use cookies and third party analytics and advertising services to enhance and manage our website and improve our business and the services we provide to you. By using the website and agreeing to this policy, you grant us permission to place and store cookies on your browser. Cookies may be used by us to collect the following information:

(a) your computer's operating system;

(b) your computer's browser type and capabilities;

(c) your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address and geolocation;

(d) web pages visited, including how you were referred to each web page; and

(e) web page usage statistics, including the time spent on each web page. 

This site uses the Google Analytics cookie, and other cookies and identifiers to collect anonymous, aggregated audience data in order to measure user interactions on our site and improve our service.   
This includes the use of Google Analytics Advertiser Features which provides Demographic and Interest reports, Remarketing, GDN Impression Reporting, and the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. 

In addition, third parties may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons or similar technologies to collect information.

Cookies can be managed by accessing the individual settings in your browser.   
For more information on how Google Analytics Advertiser Features works and to opt-out of this service, please visit the following Google support page: [ https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409?hl=en)

**2.8** We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except where required by law or in accordance with our Terms and Conditions of Use and Sale.

#### 3\. Using and Disclosing Your Personal Information

**3.1** We will generally use or disclose your personal information only for the primary purpose for which it was collected; or for a related secondary purpose where you would reasonably expect us to use or disclose the personal information for that secondary purpose. We may otherwise use and disclose your personal information if you have given us consent for the use or disclosure or it is required or authorised by law. 

**3.2** Generally, we use and disclose your personal information for the purpose of providing you with the goods or services that you have requested, or otherwise to enable us to carry out our business as an online retailer of goods and services. 

**3.3** If those purposes for which we have collected the information involve providing personal information about an individual to any third party, we will take appropriate and reasonable steps to ensure any personal information is protected. 

**3.4** We will generally only use personal information for marketing if you have given express or implied consent or it is impracticable to seek consent before this use. 

#### Consent to direct marketing and opting out

**3.5** When you register with Eat Now, you consent to Eat Now using your personal information for direct marketing purposes to communicate with you by phone, email or SMS and, if you use our mobile application, via push notification, to tell you about offers, updates and our products and services that may be of interest to you.   
You may choose to stop receiving direct marketing communications from a channel at any time by using the unsubscribe mechanism in the marketing communication itself.   
To opt-out of communications via email click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email and to opt-out of communications by SMS reply with "STOP".   
You may also decline marketing messaging sent by push notifications by refusing the relevant permission to our app in your phone or tablet settings, however this will also prevent you from receiving order updates via push. 

#### Disclosures to third parties including overseas

**3.6** We may share your information with other members of The Menulog Group Pty Ltd. Our Group is comprised of Menulog Pty Ltd and Eat Now Services Pty Ltd and their Related Bodies Corporate, as defined in the Corporations Act 2001 (Cth). 

**3.7** We may also provide your information to third parties that provide services to us, including third parties that provide our payment gateway, marketing, logistics and technology support services. This may include providing your information to third parties that are located outside of Australia. Where your personal information is transferred outside Australia (including the USA, UK, Hong Kong, the Philippines and the EU), we will do so in accordance with APP 8. In addition, we may also disclose your information to third parties in order for them to provide services to you, in accordance with our Terms and Conditions of Use and Sale and this Privacy Policy. 

#### 4\. Security of Your Personal Information

We take steps to protect the personal information we hold against loss, unauthorised access, use, modification or disclosure and against other misuse. When no longer required, personal information is destroyed in a secure manner or deleted. 

#### 5\. Access to Your Personal Information and Complaints Procedure

**5.1** Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), you have certain rights to access the personal information we collect and hold about you.

**5.2** Generally, subject to the exceptions of APP 12.3, we will allow an individual access to the personal information we hold about them within a reasonable time after it is requested. When requesting such access please identify the precise type/s of information requested. 

You may make a request by writing to us at: Privacy Inquiries, EatNow Pty Ltd, Level 23, 227 Elizabeth Street, Sydney, NSW 2000 or by email, support@eatnow.com.au. 

**5.3** We take those steps reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that the personal information that we collect, use and disclose is accurate, up to date and complete. Where an individual requests to correct information, we will take reasonable steps to correct the information, having regard to the purpose for which it is held. You may lodge a request to correct personal information in the manner outlined in clause 5.2 above. 

**5.4** To make a complaint about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles, which includes how we handle your personal information, you may contact us at the addresses provided in clause 5.2 above. We will endeavour to respond to your complaint within a reasonable time after it is received. If you are not satisfied by our response, you may acquire further information regarding privacy from the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner. 

Eat Now is owned and operated by Just Eat Holding Limited.
